<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HienThiMonAn</string>
    <string-array name="list_hinh1">
        <item>balsamicveggiepasta</item>
        <item>cajunshrimpalfredocasserole</item>
        <item>chineseblackpepperchicken</item>
        <item>crunchyasianramennoodlesalad</item>
        <item>ingredientmexicanshreddedchicken</item>
        <item>lemonyspinachcucumberorzosalad</item>
        <item>quinoatortillasoup</item>
        <item>rainbowmangoavocadospringrolls</item>
        <item>rosemarychickennoodlefood</item>
        <item>sizzlingszechuanbeefstirfry</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list_hinh2">
        <item>detail_balsamicveggiepasta</item>
        <item>detail_cajunshrimpalfredocasserole</item>
        <item>detail_chineseblackpepperchicken</item>
        <item>detail_crunchyasianramennoodlesalad</item>
        <item>detail_ingredientmexicanshreddedchicken</item>
        <item>detail_lemonyspinachcucumberorzosalad</item>
        <item>detail_quinoatortillasoup</item>
        <item>detail_rainbowmangoavocadospringrolls</item>
        <item>detail_rosemarychickennoodlefood</item>
        <item>detail_sizzlingszechuanbeefstirfry</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list_mota">
        <item>BALSAMIC VEGGIE PASTA\n
            This easy Balsamic Veggie Pasta recipe is loaded up with tons of fresh veggies and garlic, and tossed with a delicious simple balsamic vinaigrette.\n

TOTAL TIME: 35 MINS PREP TIME: 10 MINS COOK TIME: 25 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
12 ounces uncooked pasta (I used penne)\n
3 tablespoons olive oil, divided\n
1 small red onion, peeled and thinly-sliced\n
1 pound asparagus, cut into bite-sized pieces (with ends trimmed off and discarded)\n
1 small head of broccoli florets, cut into bite-sized pieces\n
1 red bell pepper, cored and thinly-sliced\n
Kosher salt and freshly-cracked black pepper\n
5 cloves garlic, peeled and minced\n
3-4 tablespoons balsamic vinegar\n
freshly-grated Parmesan cheese\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
Cook pasta in a large stock pot of generously-salted boiling water al dente according to package instructions.   \nThen drain the pasta, and set it aside.\n
Meanwhile, as the pasta water is heating and the pasta is cooking, heat 2 tablespoons oil in a large saute pan over medium-high heat.  Add the red onion and sauté, stirring occasionally, for 4 minutes.  Add the asparagus, broccoli, and red bell pepper, and season the mixture with a generous pinch of salt and pepper.  Continue sautéing for 4-5 more minutes, stirring occasionally.  (Adding in another tablespoon of oil if needed.)  Stir in the garlic and continue sautéing for 1-2 more minutes, stirring occasionally, until the garlic is fragrant.  Remove from heat.\n
Once the veggies and pasta have all finished cooking, return the stockpot to the stove over medium-high heat.  Add the remaining 1 tablespoon of oil, cooked pasta, veggie mixture, balsamic vinegar, lots of freshly-cracked black pepper, and toss to combine.  Sauté for 1-2 minutes, stirring occasionally, so that the pasta is very lightly toasted.  Taste, and add extra balsamic vinegar and black pepper if needed.
Remove from heat and sere warm, garnished with lots of Parmesan cheese.</item>
        <item>CAJUN SHRIMP ALFREDO CASSEROLE\n
This Cajun Shrimp Alfredo Casserole is full of bold and zesty flavors, it’s easy to prep ahead of time, and it’s totally comforting and delicious.  Feel free to sub in chicken or smoked sausage in place of the shrimp (or to go along with the shrimp), if you’d like.\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 40 MINS PREP TIME: 25 MINS COOK TIME: 15 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
CAJUN SHRIMP ALFREDO CASSEROLE INGREDIENTS:\n
2 pounds raw, peeled, large shrimp (tails on or off)\n
Kosher salt and freshly-cracked black pepper\n
2 tablespoons extra virgin olive oil (or butter), divided\n
2 large bell peppers, cored and thinly sliced (I used one red, one yellow)\n
1 small red onion, peeled and thinly sliced\n
2 cups sliced okra, fresh or frozen\n
2 cloves garlic, minced\n
5 cups cooked rice\n
1 batch alfredo sauce (see below)\n
toppings: lots of fresh lemon slices/wedges, finely-chopped fresh parsley, extra Parmesan cheese\n
ALFREDO SAUCE INGREDIENTS:\n
1 tablespoon extra virgin olive oil or butter\n
4 cloves garlic, pressed or finely-minced\n
3 Tablespoons all-purpose flour\n
1 cup chicken or vegetable stock (or you can use milk instead)\n
1 cup milk (I used 2%)\n
3/4 cup freshly-grated Parmesan cheese\n
1 tablespoon Old Bay seasoning\n
1/4 teaspoon Kosher salt + 1/4 teaspoon freshly-cracked black pepper\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
TO MAKE THE CAJUN SHRIMP ALFREDO CASSEROLE:\n
Heat oven to 350°F.\n
Season the shrimp on both sides with a few pinches of salt and pepper.  Heat 1 tablespoon olive oil (or melt butter) in a large sauté pan over medium-high heat.  Add the shrimp and sauté for 5 minutes, stirring and flipping occasionally, until the shrimp are pink and cooked through.  Transfer shrimp with a slotted spoon to a clean plate, and set aside.
Heat the remaining olive oil (or butter) in the sauté pan.  Add bell peppers and onion, and cook for 5 minutes, stirring occasionally.  Add in the okra and garlic, and cook for 3 more minutes, stirring occasionally.\n
Transfer the cooked shrimp, veggie mixture, rice and alfredo sauce to a large mixing bowl, and toss until evenly combined.  Pour the mixture into a 9 x 13-inch baking dish, and spread out evenly.\n
Bake uncovered for 15 minutes.  Remove from oven, and serve immediately, garnished with toppings (including lots of fresh lemon juice, it’s a must!).\n
TO MAKE THE ALFREDO SAUCE:\n
Heat olive oil (or melt butter) in a large sauté pan over medium-high heat. Add garlic and sauté one minute, stirring occasionally, until fragrant. Sprinkle with flour, and stir to combine. Sauté for an additional minute to cook the flour, stirring occasionally.\n
Slowly pour in the chicken broth, whisking to combine until smooth. Whisk in milk until combined, and bring the mixture to a simmer.  (Be careful not to let it boil.)  Reduce heat to medium-low, and cook for an additional minute until the sauce has thickened.  Then add in the Parmesan cheese, Old Bay, salt and pepper, and stir until the cheese melted.  Remove from heat and set aside.</item>
        <item>BLACK PEPPER CHICKEN\n
This restaurant-style Chinese Black Pepper Chicken recipe is quick and easy to make at home, totally versatile if you’d like to sub in different veggies or proteins, and so comforting and delicious.\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 20 MINS PREP TIME: 7 MINS COOK TIME: 13 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
2 tablespoons peanut oil (or any mild-flavored oil), divided\n
1 pound boneless skinless chicken breasts, cut into bite-sized pieces\n
1 small bell pepper, cored and thinly-sliced\n
1 small red onion, peeled and thinly-sliced\n
2 stalks celery, thinly-sliced on a bias\n
2 cloves garlic, peeled and minced\n
1/4 cup low-sodium soy sauce\n
1 tablespoon cornstarch\n
1 tablespoon oyster sauce\n
1 tablespoon rice wine vinegar\n
2 teaspoons freshly-cracked black pepper (or more to taste)\n
1/4 teaspoon ground ginger\n
optional toppings: thinly-sliced green onions, toasted sesame seeds\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
Heat 1 tablespoon oil over medium-high heat in a large sauté pan or wok.  Add chicken and sauté for 4-5 minutes, stirring occasionally, until the chicken is cooked through and no longer pink on the inside.  Use a slotted spoon to transfer the chicken to a clean plate, and set aside.\n
Add the remaining 1 tablespoon oil to the sauté pan, along with the bell pepper, onion, celery and garlic.  Sauté for 5-6 more minutes, stirring occasionally.\n
Meanwhile, as the veggies are sautéing, whisk together the soy sauce, cornstarch, oyster sauce, vinegar, black pepper and ginger in a small bowl until combined.\n
Once the veggies are ready go to, add the chicken and sauce mixture to the pan, and stir until the veggies and chicken are evenly coated.  Continue to cook for 1-2 minutes, or until the sauce has thickened.  Taste, and season with extra soy sauce and/or black pepper as desired.\n
Remove from heat, and serve immediately, sprinkled with your desired toppings.\n
If you would like a spicier dish, feel free to stir in a teaspoon or two of garlic chili sauce into the sauce.</item>
        <item>CRUNCHY ASIAN RAMEN NOODLE SALAD
            (A.K.A. BASICALLY THE BEST POTLUCK SALAD EVER)\n
This delicious Crunchy Asian Ramen Noodle Salad recipe is tossed with a simple sesame vinaigrette…and tastes absolutely delicious!\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 10 MINS PREP TIME: 10 MINS COOK TIME: 0 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
SALAD INGREDIENTS:\n
1 (16-ounce) bag coleslaw mix\n
2 (3-ounce) packages of ramen noodles*, crumbled (you will not use the seasoning packet)\n
1 cup shelled and cooked edamame\n
1 avocado, peeled, pitted and diced\n
1 mango, peeled, pitted, and julienned (or diced)\n
1/2 cup thinly-sliced almonds\n
1/2 cup thinly-sliced green onions (scallions)\n
Asian honey vinaigrette (see ingredients below)\n
ASIAN HONEY VINAIGRETTE\n
1/2 cup avocado oil (or vegetable oil, or any cooking oil)\n
1/4 cup honey (or your desired sweetener)\n
1/4 cup rice vinegar\n
2 teaspoons soy sauce\n
1/4 teaspoon toasted sesame oil\n
pinch of salt and black pepper\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
TO MAKE THE SALAD:\n
Heat oven to 425°F. Spread the crumbled ramen noodles and sliced almonds out on a baking sheet, and stir a bit to combine. Bake for about 5 minutes, or until the almonds and noodles are slightly toasted and golden. Remove baking sheet, and give the mixture a good stir to toss. Then return it to the oven and toast for an additional 3 minutes. Keep a very close eye on the mixture so that it does not burn. Remove and set aside.\n
Add ingredients (including the vinaigrette) together in a large bowl, and toss until combined.\n
Serve immediately, or cover and refrigerate for up to 3 days. (This salad is much better eaten the first day, as the noodles lose their “crunch” the longer it sits, and the avocado may brown a bit. Still, it’s perfectly edible and enjoyable even after a few days!)\n
TO MAKE THE VINAIGRETTE:\n
Whisk all ingredients together until combined.\n
*You can use any kind of packaged ramen noodles for this recipe.  If you’d like organic (and less-processed) alternatives to the classic $0.30 packets at the grocery store, I recommend these organic classic ramen noodles or organic brown rice ramen noodles.\n
\n
**I also like sprinkling mine with some toasted sesame seeds (I used black sesame seeds in the photo), but that’s totally optional.</item>
        <item>INGREDIENT MEXICAN SHREDDED CHICKEN\n
This 3-Ingredient Mexican Shredded Chicken recipe is full of great flavor, easy to make in the Instant Pot or Crock-Pot, and perfect for tacos, burritos, quesadillas, salads and more!\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 48 MINS PREP TIME: 3 MINS COOK TIME: 45 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
2.5 to 3 pounds boneless skinless chicken breasts (or thighs)\n
2 cups (16 ounces) salsa*, homemade or store-bought\n
1 packet McCormick Original Taco Seasoning\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
Instant Pot Method: Add chicken, salsa and taco seasoning to the bowl of your Instant Pot, and toss briefly to combine.  Close lid securely and set vent to “Sealing”.  Press “Manual”, then press “Pressure” until the light on “High Pressure” lights up, then adjust the +/- buttons until time reads 30 minutes.  Cook.  Then very carefully, turn the vent to “Venting” for quick release, and wait until all of the steam has released and the valve has dropped.  Remove the lid.  Continue with step 3 below.\n
Crock-Pot Method: Add chicken, salsa and taco seasoning to the bowl of your slow cooker, and toss briefly to combine.  Cover and cook on high for 3-4 hours or on low for 6-8 hours until the chicken shreds easily with a fork.\n
Shred the chicken with two forks, then give the chicken a good toss with the remaining juices.\n
Serve immediately.  Or store in an airtight container in the refrigerator for up to 3 days, or in the freezer for up to 3 months.\n
*A few people have mentioned getting a “burn” message on their Instant Pot.  I’ve never experienced this, but just to be safe, if you are using a thick/chunky salsa, stir in an extra 1/2 cup water along with the salsa.</item>
        <item>HERB-LOVERS LEMONY ORZO SALAD\n
This Herb-Lovers Lemony Orzo Salad is full of fresh and zesty ingredients that everyone will love!  Perfect for serving as a main dish or side, and easy to customize with your favorite add-ins.\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 30 MINS PREP TIME: 15 MINS COOK TIME: 15 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
12 ounces uncooked orzo (or any pasta shape)\n
2 large handfuls fresh baby spinach, chopped\n
1 (15-ounce) can chickpeas (garbanzo beans), rinsed and drained\n
1 English cucumber, diced\n
half a small red onion, diced\n
1 cup roughly-chopped fresh basil leaves\n
1 cup roughly-chopped fresh mint leaves\n
1-2 lemons, zested and juiced\n
1/4 cup olive oil\n
sea salt and freshly-cracked black pepper, to taste\n
optional: 1/2 cup crumbled feta or goat cheese\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
Cook the pasta in a large stockpot of generously-salted water until al dente, according to package instructions.  Drain pasta then rinse thoroughly in a strainer with cold water until the pasta is chilled.  Transfer pasta to a large mixing bowl.\n
Add the remaining ingredients to the mixing bowl (using cheese if desired).  Toss until evenly combined.  Taste, and season with a few generous pinches of salt and pepper, to taste.  (I used about 1 teaspoon each of salt and pepper.)  Also feel free to add in extra lemon juice if you’d like an extra-lemony salad.  (My fave.)\n
Serve immediately.  Or cover and refrigerate for up to 3 days.</item>
        <item>QUINOA TORTILLA SOUP\n
This Quinoa Tortilla Soup recipe is made with the most amazing zesty chile broth, it’s naturally vegetarian, vegan and gluten-free, and totally hearty and delicious.  Pile yours high with your favorite toppings!\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 40 MINS PREP TIME: 15 MINS COOK TIME: 25 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
2-4 dried pasilla chiles, stemmed and seeded*\n
2 (15-ounce) cans fire-roasted diced tomatoes\n
6 cups vegetable stock, divided\n
1 tablespoon olive oil\n
1 medium white onion, peeled and diced\n
4 cloves garlic, peeled and minced\n
2 (15-ounce) cans beans of your choice, rinsed and drained (I used one can pinto, one can black beans)\n
1/2 cup whole kernel corn\n
1/2 cup uncooked quinoa, rinsed and drained\n
2 teaspoons ground cumin\n
sea salt and freshly-cracked black pepper\n
toppings: lots of tortilla strips (or crumbled up tortilla chips), diced fresh avocado, chopped fresh cilantro, diced red onion, fresh lime wedges\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
To Prepare The Chiles: If you have a gas range, briefly toast the chiles by holding them a few inches above the open flame, rotating to toast on all sides, until fragrant.  If you have an electric range, heat your stockpot over medium-high heat and toast the chiles in the dry pot for a minute or so, pressing them down with a wooden spoon or spatula, and rotating to toast on all sides, until fragrant.  Transfer the chiles* to a blender or food processor along with 1 can of the tomatoes and 1 cup of vegetable stock.  Puree for 1 minute or until completely smooth.  Set aside.\n
Heat oil in the large stockpot over medium-high heat.  Add onion and sauté for 5 minutes, stirring occasionally, until soft and translucent.  Add in the garlic and sauté for 1-2 more minutes, stirring occasionally, until fragrant.  Add in the remaining can of tomatoes, vegetable stock, beans, corn, quinoa, cumin, and the pureed chile mixture.  Stir to combine.\n
Continue cooking the soup until it reaches a simmer.  Then reduce heat to medium-low, cover, and continue to simmer until the quinoa is completely cooked, stirring occasionally.\n
Taste and season with a few generous pinches of salt and pepper, as needed.\n
Serve immediately, garnished with lots of your favorite toppings.  Or store in sealed containers in the refrigerator for up to 3 days, or freeze for up to 3 months.\n
*A few notes about the pasilla chiles:\n
\n
They are considered to have a “medium” heat level.  So if you’re not a fan of spicy food, I would recommend starting with 1 or 2 chiles.  Then taste your soup once it’s ready to go.  And if you would like to add more chiles, you can always puree 1 or 2 more with a cup or two of your broth at the end of the cooking time.\n
If your grocery store does not carry dried pasilla chiles, you can order them online.  Or you can substitute ancho chiles, which will be slightly sweeter.  Or guajillo chiles, which will be a bit spicier.</item>
        <item>MANGO AVOCADO SPRING ROLLS (WITH PEANUT SAUCE)\n
These Mango Avocado Spring Rolls are filled with a rainbow of fresh and delicious ingredients, and served with the most irresistible peanut dipping sauce.\n
\n
TOTAL TIME: 30 MINS PREP TIME: 30 MINS COOK TIME: 0 MINS\n
INGREDIENTS:\n
SPRING ROLL INGREDIENTS:\n
2 ounces rice stick (vermicelli) noodles\n
2 mangoes, peeled, cored and thinly sliced\n
2 avocados, peeled, pitted and thinly sliced\n
2 carrots, thinly sliced\n
1 English cucumber, thinly sliced\n
quarter of a small red cabbage, thinly sliced\n
1 bunch fresh cilantro leaves\n
1 bunch fresh mint leaves\n
10-12 spring roll wrappers\n
PEANUT SAUCE INGREDIENTS:\n
1/3 cup natural peanut butter\n
2 tablespoons hoisin sauce\n
1 tablespoon low-sodium soy sauce (or tamari)\n
1 tablespoon rice vinegar\n
1/2 teaspoon chili garlic sauce (or more, to taste)\n
1/4 teaspoon sesame oil\n
1/3 cup warm water\n
DIRECTIONS:\n
\n
\nTo Make The Peanut Sauce: Whisk all ingredients together in a small bowl until combined.  If you would like a thinner sauce, whisk in more water.
\nTo Make The Spring Rolls: Cook thin rice vermicelli noodles according to package directions.  Once they are al dente, transfer the noodles to a strainer and rinse with cold water until the noodles are completely chilled.  Toss the thoroughly with a drizzle of oil (I like using sesame oil) to prevent the noodles from sticking together.  Set aside.
\nFill a large shallow pan with warm water (a sauté pan or pie dish works great).  Lay a spring roll wrapper in the hot water and let it rest there for about 20-30 seconds until soft, but not mushy.  Transfer the spring roll wrapper to plate (or a clean towel spread out on a flat surface, which will help the wrapper not to stick).
\nArrange your fillings in the center of the wrapper in a vertical line.  Fold in the top and bottom sides of the wrapper.  Then fold over the left side of the wrapper, tightly tucking in the fillings, and roll the wrapper to the right until it is sealed.
\nServe immediately with the peanut dipping sauce and/or nuoc cham, or refrigerate in a sealed container for up to 3 days.</item>
        <item>ROSEMARY CHICKEN NOODLE SOUP\n
\nThis Rosemary Chicken Noodle Soup recipe is kicked up a notch with the addition of lots of fresh aromatic rosemary, and it’s ready to go in about 30 minutes!
\n
\nTOTAL TIME: 30 MINS PREP TIME: 8 MINS COOK TIME: 22 MINS
\nINGREDIENTS:
\n2 Tablespoons olive oil
\n1 small white onion, peeled and diced
\n2 medium carrots, peeled and diced
\n2 stalks celery, ends trimmed and diced
\n3 cloves garlic, minced or pressed
\n8 cups (64 ounces) good-quality chicken stock
\n3-4 stalks *fresh rosemary (or more/less to taste)
\n6 ounces wide egg noodles (or use gluten-free noodles if making this GF)
\n2 cups shredded cooked chicken
\nsalt and pepper
\n(optional: chopped fresh parsley for garnish)
\nDIRECTIONS:
\n
\nHeat oil in a large stockpot over medium-high heat.  Add onion and saute for 4 minutes, stirring occasionally.  Add carrots and celery and saute for another 3-4 minutes, or until the carrots are softened a bit.  Add garlic and saute for an additional 1-2 minutes, or until fragrant.  Add chicken stock and stir until combined.  Gently stir the rosemary into the soup, then continue cooking until the soup reaches a simmer.  Reduce heat to medium, and simmer for an additional 5 minutes until the broth has your desired level of rosemary flavor.  (You can add in more rosemary if needed.)
\n
\nOnce the broth is ready, remove the rosemary, and stir in the egg noodles and chicken.  Continue cooking for 8-10 minutes or until the egg noodles are al dente.  (The longer they cook, the more broth they will soak up.  Feel free to add more chicken stock if desired.)  Season the soup with salt and pepper to taste.
\n
\nServe warm, garnished with extra black pepper and fresh parsley if desired.
\n
\n
\n
\n*A few important notes about rosemary:
\n
\nIf fresh rosemary is not available, you can substitute 2-3 teaspoons (or more) of dried rosemary.  Or 1.5 teaspoons (or more) ground rosemary.  I always recommend starting with less, and then you can always add more if desired.
\n
\nAlso, I’m not a big fan of eating rosemary needles, so I prefer to let the sprigs simmer in the broth until most of their flavor is released, and then just removing them before serving.  But heads up — they soften and tend to fall apart after they simmer for quite awhile.  So I recommend letting them simmer on top of the stock so that you can remove them easily.  As an alternative, you can also mince them up finely and just eat them with the soup.
\n
\nTo each, her or his own when it comes to rosemary preferences.  ;)</item>
        <item>SIZZLIN SPICY SZECHUAN STIR-FRY\n
\nThis Sizzlin Spicy Szechuan Stir-Fry is quick and easy to make with beef, chicken, shrimp or tofu.  Feel free to make it as spicy or mild as you prefer!
\n
\nTOTAL TIME: 20 MINS PREP TIME: 10 MINS COOK TIME: 10 MINS
\nINGREDIENTS:
\n2 tablespoons avocado oil (or other high-heat oil), divided
\n1 pound flank steak, thinly-sliced
\n1 medium white onion, peeled and thinly sliced
\n1 large red bell pepper, cored and thinly sliced
\n4 cloves garlic, peeled and thinly sliced
\n1 batch Szechuan Sauce
\noptional toppings: thinly-sliced green onions, toasted sesame seeds, extra crushed red pepper flakes
\nDIRECTIONS:
\n
\nHeat 1 tablespoon oil in a wok or large sauté pan over high heat.
\nAdd steak and sauté for 4-5 minutes, tossing occasionally, until cooked through.  Transfer steak to a clean plate and set aside.
\nAdd the remaining 1 tablespoon oil to the pan, along with the onion and bell pepper.  Sauté for 3-4 minutes, tossing occasionally, until cooked by still slightly crispy.  (I don’t like my veggies to be too soft in a stir-fry.)  Add garlic and sauté for 1 more minute, or until fragrant.
\nReduce heat to medium.  Add the steak and Szechuan sauce to the veggies, and toss to combine for about 30 seconds, or until the sauce thickens up.
\nRemove from heat and serve immediately over rice or noodles, sprinkled with your desired toppings.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="list_ten">
        <item>BALSAMIC VEGGIE PASTA</item>
        <item>CAJUN SHRIMP ALFREDO CASSEROLE</item>
        <item>BLACK PEPPER CHICKEN</item>
        <item>CRUNCHY ASIAN RAMEN NOODLE SALAD</item>
        <item>INGREDIENT MEXICAN SHREDDED CHICKEN</item>
        <item>HERB-LOVERS LEMONY ORZO SALAD</item>
        <item>QUINOA TORTILLA SOUP</item>
        <item>MANGO AVOCADO SPRING ROLLS</item>
        <item>ROSEMARY CHICKEN NOODLE SOUP</item>
        <item>SIZZLIN' SPICY SZECHUAN STIR-FRY</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
